Guide to the Records of the Student Senators Council RG.44.0.1
New York University Archives
- Series IV: Memos and Reports, 1976-2014; 14.88 Linear Feet in 34 manuscript boxes
  - Election of Officers, 1995-1996 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - External Affairs/Albany Day, 1995-1996 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Memos to and from Administrators, 1995-1996 (Box 69, Folder 8-9, Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Photographic Chemical Recycling, 1995-1996 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Protest & Dissent, Policy On, 1995-1996 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Rice Commission (CIC), 1995-1996 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Security, 1995-1996 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Space, 1995-1996 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Student/Faculty Relations, 1995-1996 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Academic Issues (Ad Hoc), 1996-1997 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Alumni Relations, 1996-1997 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Campus Media, 1996-1997 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Commuter Students, 1996-1997 (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Computers (NYU Net, Internet), 1996-1997 (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Distinguished Teachers, 1996-1997 (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Equal Commission, 1996-1997 (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - Forum, 1996-1997 (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - General Studies Program (SCE), 1996-1997 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Information Sent to SSC/UCSL, 1996-1997 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Inquiries from the Student Body, 1996-1997 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Memos to and from Administrators, 1996-1997 (Box 71, Folder 4-5)
  - Rice Commission (CIC), 1996-1997 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Special Interest Housing Board, 1996-1997 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Student/Faculty Relations, 1996-1997 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Student Services (Food, Health), 1996-1997 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Washington Square News, 1996-1997 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Academic Support Services, 1997-1998 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Campus Media, 1997-1998 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Commuter Students, 1997-1998 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Computers (NYU Net, Internet), 1997-1998 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Equal Commission, 1997-1998 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - External Affairs/Albany Day, 1997-1998 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Forum, 1997-1998 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - General Studies Program (SCE), 1997-1998 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Memorandum, 1997-1998 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Memos to and from Administrators, 1997-1998 (Box 72, Folder 10-11)
  - Protest and Dissent (Policy On), 1997-1998 (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Rice Commission (CIC), 1997-1998 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Student/Faculty Relations, 1997-1998 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Student Services (Food, Health), 1997-1998 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Student Survey: Reality Check, 1997-1998 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - New York University Health Center Five-Year Strategic Plan (Draft Revision), 1998 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Strategies for Hiring Underrepresented Faculty, 1998 (Box 73, Folder 6-7)
  - Academic Support Services, 1998-1999 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Code of Conduct: Sportswear Logos, 1998-1999 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Computers (NYU Net, Internet), 1998-1999 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Distinguished Teachers, 1998-1999 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - External Affairs/Albany Day, 1998-1999 (Box 73, Folder 12, Box 74, Folder 1)
  - FERPA, 1998-1999 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Forum, 1998-1999 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Information Sent to SSC/UCSL, 1998-1999 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Memos to and from Administrators, 1998-1999 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Washington Square News, 1998-1999 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Alumni, 1999-2000 (Box 74, Folder 7, Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Distinguished Teachers, 1999-2000 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Forum, 1999-2000 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - General Information, 1999-2000 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Graduate Assistant Unionization, 1999-2000 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Information Sent to SSC/UCSL, 1999-2000 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Memos to Admin, 1999-2000 (Box 75, Folder 7-8)
  - Student/Faculty Relations, 1999-2000 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Washington Square News, 1999-2000 (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Academic Priorities, 2000-2001 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Academic Support Services, 2000-2001 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Forum, 2000-2001 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - General Information, 2000-2001 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Graduate Student Unionization, 2000-2001 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Information Sent to SSC/UCSL, 2000-2001 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Kimmel Center, 2000-2001 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Memos to and from Administrators, 2000-2001 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - President Oliva's Resignation, 2000-2001 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Protest and Dissent, Policy On, 2000-2001 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Sexual Harrassment, 2000-2001 (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - Washington Square News, 2000-2001 (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - Academic Support Services, 2001-2002 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Alumni Relations, 2001-2002 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Coordinated Election Period, 2001-2002 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - External Affairs/Albany Day, 2001-2002 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Forum, 2001-2002 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - General Information, 2001-2002 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Graduate Affairs, 2001-2002 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Graduate Assistant Unionization, 2001-2002 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - International Students, 2001-2002 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Memos to and from Administrators, 2001-2002 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - NYU T-Shirts, 2001-2002 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - President Service Awards, 2001-2002 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Presidential Transition, 2001-2002 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Protest and Dissent, Policy On, 2001-2002 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Sexual Misconduct, 2001-2002 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Student Guest Speakers, 2001-2002 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Student Services, 2001-2002 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Washington Square News, 2001-2002 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - World Trade Center Disaster, 2001-2002 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Albany Day, 2002-2003 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Arab Students United at NYU, 2002-2003 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Chairs First Reports - General, 2002-2003 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Challenge Fund, 2002-2003 (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - Commencement, 2002-2003 (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - Commuter Students, 2002-2003 (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - Deans Working Group, 2002-2003 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Distinguished Teachers, 2002-2003 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Election of Officers, 2002-2003 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - External Affairs/Albany Day, 2002-2003 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - FERPA, 2002-2003 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Forum, 2002-2003 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Hindle Report April 1971, University Purposes & Guidelines, 2002-2003 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Information Sent to SSC/UCSL, 2002-2003 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Kimmel Center, 2002-2003 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Memos to and from Administrators, 2002-2003 (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Memorandum & Reports, 2002-2008 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Memos to the President, 2002-2003 (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Middle States, 2002-2003 (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - Roundtables, 2002-2003 (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - School of Medicine/Health Enterprise, 2002-2003 (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - Solomon Amendment, 2002-2003 (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - Transgender, 2002-2003 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Childhood Program, 2003 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Graduate Student Initiative, 2003 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Academic Support Services, 2003-2004 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Chair's First Reports SSC/UCSL Generic, 2003-2004 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Commencement, 2003-2004 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Coordination Election Period, 2003-2004 (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - Enterprise Communications, 2003-2004 (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Forum, 2003-2004 (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - Graduate Student Initiative, 2003-2004 (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - Memos to and from Administrators, 2003-2004 (Box 80, Folder 12)
  - Middle States, 2003-2004 (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Student Affairs/Activities, 2003-2004 (Box 80, Folder 14)
  - Student Services, 2003-2004 (Box 80, Folder 15)
  - Washington Square News, 2003-2004 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Academic Support Services, 2004-2005 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Childcare, 2004-2005 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Committee Chairs (Reports), 2004-2005 (Box 81, Folder 4-5)
  - External Affair/Albany Day, 2004-2005 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - FERPA, 2004-2005 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Forum, 2004-2005 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Graduate Assistant Unionization, 2004-2005 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Information Sent to SSC/UCSL, 2004-2005 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Memos to and from Administrators, 2004-2005 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Middle States, 2004-2005 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Student/Faculty Relations, 2004-2005 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Washington Square News, 2004-2005 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Committee Reports, 2005-2006 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Coordinated Election Period, 2005-2006 (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Election of Officers, 2005-2006 (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Forum, 2005-2006 (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Graduate Assisstant Grievances, 2005-2006 (Box 82, Folder 11-12)
  - Graduate Assistant Unionization Working Group, 2005-2006 (Box 82, Folder 13, Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Memos to and from Administrators, 2005-2006 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Orientation, 2005-2006 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Washington Square News, 2005-2006 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - External Affairs/Albany Day, 2006-2007 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - NYU 2031, 2006-2007 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Orientation, 2006-2007 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - UCSL Committee Reports, 2006-2007 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - 2031 Plan, 2007-2008 (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Committee Reports, 2007-2008 (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - Commuter Students, 2007-2008 (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - External Affairs/Albany Day, 2007-2008 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - FERPA, 2007-2008 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Memos to and from Administrators, 2007-2008 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Middle States, 2007-2008 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Orientation, 2007-2008 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - School Reports, 2007-2009 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Washington Square News, 2007-2008 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Non-Tenure Track Full Time Faculty Report, 2008 (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Abu Dhabi Trip, 2008-2009 (Box 84, Folder 9-10)
  - Affinity Partnership, 2008-2009 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Commuter Students, 2008-2009 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Election of Officers, 2008-2009 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - FERPA, 2008-2009 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Memos to and from Administrators, 2008-2009 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Public Affairs, 2008-2009 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - UCSL Committee Reports, 2008-2009 (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - Reengineering II Task Force Reports, 2009 (Box 85, Folder 8-9)
  - Revenue Re-Engineering Task Force Final Report, 2009 (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - Minutes & Reports, 2012 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - End of Semester Reports, 2014 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Mid-Fall Committee Reports, 2014 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - New York University: Self-Study Report of Multischool, Interdisciplinary Programs for the Middle States Commission on Higher Education, 2014 (Box 86, Folder 4-5)
  - NYU.EDU, 2014 (Box 86, Folder 6)
- Series V: Governance and Policy, 1976-2012; 5.25 Linear Feet in 12 manuscript boxes
  Series V contains materials related to the governance and policies of the Student Senators Council, as well as how they changed over time. Copies of the "Rules of Procedure," additional by-laws, and resolutions are found in this series. This series also contains some materials from the Organization and Governance committee, as well as any constitutions from councils under the SSC.
  - Constitution (Updated in September 1978), 1976 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Rules of Procedure, 1976 (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - All Square Student Activities Budget Committee (ASSABC) Constitution and Early Documents, 1976-1977 (Box 241, Folder 6-7)
  - Constitution: School of the Arts Student Council, 1976-1977 (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - Constitution: School of Continuing Education (SCE) Degree Students' Council, 1977 (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - Proposed Constitution for Student Activities Board (Rejected), 1977 (Box 86, Folder 11)
  - Proposed Constitution of the Student Activities Board (Rejected), 1977 (Box 242, Folder 3)
  - Senate Rules of Procedure, 1977 (Box 86, Folder 12)
  - Judiciary (Rejected 2/78), 1977-1978 (Box 86, Folder 13)
  - NYU Student Disciplinary Procedures Senate Approved 2/9/78, 1977-1978 (Box 86, Folder 14)
  - Resolutions Passed, 1977-1978 (Box 86, Folder 15)
  - Senate Committee on Organization and Governance (SCOG), 1977-1978 (Box 86, Folder 16)
  - Senate Committee on Organization and Governance (SCOG) Student Disciplinary Procedures, 1977-1978 (Box 86, Folder 17)
  - Graduate Student Organization (GSO) - School of Education, Health, Nursing, and Arts Professions (SEHNAP) Letter to Sawhill, 1978 (Box 86, Folder 18)
  - All Square Student Activities Budget Committee (ASSABC) Rules, 1978-1979 (Box 243, Folder 16)
  - Constitution, 1978-1979 (Box 86, Folder 19)
  - Student Senators Council-By Law 43, 1978-1979 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Organization & Governance, 1979-1980 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Resolutions, 1979-1980 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Senate Rules of Procedure, 1979-1980 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - All Square Student Activities Budget Committee (ASSABC) Rules Re: Membership, etc…, 1980-1981 (Box 245, Folder 9)
  - Bylaw 43, 1980-1981 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Organization & Governance, 1980-1981 (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Resolutions, 1980-1981 (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Student Activities Board (SAB) Rules of Procedure, 1980-1981 (Box 246, Folder 8)
  - Students' Bill of Rights, 1980-1981 (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - Termination of Programs Rights, 1980-1981 (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - UCSL Constitution, 1980-1981 (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - WSVC Student Council, 1980-1981 (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - Bylaw 43, 1981-1982 (Box 87, Folder 12)
  - Dismissal for Cause, 1981-1982 (Box 87, Folder 13)
  - Election Guidelines, 1981-1982 (Box 87, Folder 14)
  - Election of Officers, 1981-1982 (Box 87, Folder 15)
  - Organization & Governance, 1981-1982 (Box 87, Folder 16)
  - Resolutions, 1981-1982 (Box 87, Folder 17)
  - Senate Description & Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 87, Folder 18)
  - Senate Rules of Procedure, 1981-1982 (Box 87, Folder 19)
  - Student Activities Board (SAB) Rules of Procedure, 1981-1982 (Box 246, Folder 17)
  - Students' Bill of Rights, 1981-1982 (Box 87, Folder 20)
  - Student Grievance Procedures, 1981-1982 (Box 87, Folder 21)
  - UCSL Bylaws and Constitution, 1981-1982 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Alcohol Policies (SAB), 1982-1983 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Bylaw #43, 1982-1983 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Bylaws 43c: UCSL only, 1982-1983 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Organization & Governance, 1982-1983 (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - Resolutions, 1982-1983 (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - Senate Rules of Procedure, 1982-1983 (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - SSC Proposed Rules of Procedure, 1982-1983 (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - UCSL Bylaws and Constitution, 1982-1983 (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Senate Rules of Procedure, 1983 (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Bylaw 43 (SSC only), 1983-1984 (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - Bylaws 43c (UCSL only), 1983-1984 (Box 88, Folder 12)
  - Organization & Governance: SCOG, 1983-1984 (Box 88, Folder 13)
  - Parliamentary Procedure, 1983-1984 (Box 88, Folder 14)
  - SSC Proposed Rules of Procedure, 1983-1984 (Box 88, Folder 15)
  - SSC Rules of Procedure Draft, 1983-1984 (Box 88, Folder 16)
  - UCSL Proposed Rules of Procedure, 1983-1984 (Box 88, Folder 17)
  - UCSL Reorganization: Proposed, 1983-1984 (Box 88, Folder 18)
  - Proposed Amendment to UCSL Constitution - Merger of Student Activities Board (SAB) and All Square Student Activities Budget Committee (ASSABC), 1984 (Box 88, Folder 19)
  - Resolutions, 1984 (Box 88, Folder 20)
  - Senate Rules of Procedure, 1984 (Box 88, Folder 21)
  - University Council on Student UCSL Constitution, 1984 (Box 88, Folder 22)
  - Bylaw 31: The Senate, 1984-1985 (Box 88, Folder 23)
  - Bylaw 43 SSC, 1984-1985 (Box 88, Folder 24)
  - Bylaw 43c UCSL only, 1984-1985 (Box 88, Folder 25)
  - Chapter III: University Senate, 1984-1985 (Box 88, Folder 26)
  - Resolutions, 1984-1985 (Box 88, Folder 27)
  - Senate Rules of Procedure, 1984-1985 (Box 88, Folder 28)
  - SSC Rules of Procedure, 1984-1985 (Box 89, Folder 28)
  - Student Government Handbook, 1984-1985 (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - UCSL Rules of Procedure, 1984-1985 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - New York University Student Senators Council - Student Government Handbook, 1985-1986 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Student Government Handbook, 1985-1986 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Election of Officers, 1986-1987 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - NYU Student Senators Council Student Government Handbook, 1986-1987 (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Rules & Procedure, 1986-1987 (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - Vice Chairperson, 1986-1987 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Election of Officers, 1987-1988 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - New York University Student Senators Council - Student Government Handbook, 1987-1988 (Box 90, Folder 3- 5)
  - Organization & Governance (SCOG), 1987-1988 (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Student Government Handbooks, 1987-1988 (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - Bylaw Changes effective June 1989, 1988 (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - New York University Student Senators Council - Student Government Handbook, 1988-1989 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Organization & Governance (SCOG), 1988-1989 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Rules & Organization Comm. (SSC), 1988-1989 (Box 177, Folder 8)
  - NYU Charter and Bylaws, 1989 (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - Bylaw 31 University Senate, 1989-1990 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Bylaw 43 Student Senators Council, 1989-1990 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Governance Chart, 1989-1990 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Organization & Governance (SCOG), 1989-1990 (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - Rules of Procedure, 1989-1990 (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - Election of Officers, 1990-1991 (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - Organization & Governance (SCOG), 1990-1991 (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Protest and Dissent, Guidelines, 1990-1991 (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - Bylaw 31 University Senate, 1991-1992 (Box 91, Folder 11)
  - Bylaw 43 Student Senators Council, 1991-1992 (Box 91, Folder 12)
  - Election of Officers, 1991-1992 (Box 91, Folder 13)
  - Rules & Organization, 1991-1992 (Box 91, Folder 14)
  - Bylaw 31: University Senate, 1992-1993 (Box 91, Folder 15)
  - Bylaw 43: Student Senators Council, 1992-1993 (Box 91, Folder 16)
  - Bylaw 43(c): UCSL, 1992-1993 (Box 91, Folder 17)
  - Election of Officers, 1992-1993 (Box 91, Folder 18)
  - Organization & Governance (SCOG), 1992-1993 (Box 132, Folder 2)
  - Protest & Dissent, Guidelines, 1992-1993 (Box 91, Folder 19)
  - Purpose and Status: UCSL, 1992-1993 (Box 91, Folder 20)
  - Resolutions, 1992-1993 (Box 91, Folder 21)
  - Rules and Organization, 1992-1993 (Box 91, Folder 22)
  - Various Rules of Procedure, 1992-1993 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Bylaw 31, 1993 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Bylaw 31: University Senate, 1993-1994 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Bylaw 43: Student Senators Council, 1993-1994 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Bylaw 43 (c): UCSL, 1993-1994 (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Election of Officers, 1993-1994 (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Organization & Governance (SCOG), 1993-1994 (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - Organizational Structure, 1993-1994 (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - Rules and Organization, 1993-1994 (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - Student Government Handbook, 1994 (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - Bylaw 31: Senate, 1994-1995 (Box 92, Folder 11)
  - Bylaw 31: University Senate, 1994-1995 (Box 92, Folder 12)
  - Bylaw 43: SSC, 1994-1995 (Box 92, Folder 13)
  - Bylaw 43: Student Senate Council (2 versions: SSC & UCSL), 1994-1995 (Box 92, Folder 14)
  - Bylaw 43 (c): UCSL, 1994-1995 (Box 92, Folder 15)
  - Election of Officers, 1994-1995 (Box 92, Folder 16)
  - Organization & Governance, 1994-1995 (Box 92, Folder 17)
  - Resolutions, 1994-1995 (Box 92, Folder 18)
  - Bylaw 31: University Senate, 1995-1996 (Box 92, Folder 19)
  - Bylaw 43: SSC (2 versions, SSC & UCSL), 1995-1996 (Box 92, Folder 20)
  - Organization & Governance (SCOG), 1995-1996 (Box 92, Folder 21)
  - Resolutions, 1995-1996 (Box 92, Folder 22)
  - Rules & Organization, 1995-1996 (Box 92, Folder 23, Box 93, Folder 1)
  - All Square Student Activities Budget Committee (ASSABC) Rules, 1996, 1999, 2007-2008 (Box 249, Folder 9)
  - Bylaw 43: SSC, SSC & UCSL - 2 versions, 1996-1997 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Election of Officers, 1996-1997 (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Organization & Governance (SCOG), 1996-1997 (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Resolutions, 1996-1997 (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Rules and Organization, 1996-1997 (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Bylaw 31: University Senate, 1997-1998 (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - Bylaw 43: SSC (2 versions SSC and UCSL), 1997-1998 (Box 93, Folder 9)
  - Bylaws, 1997 (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - Election of Officers, 1997-1998 (Box 93, Folder 10)
  - Organization and Governance, 1997-1998 (Box 93, Folder 11)
  - Resolutions, 1997-1998 (Box 93, Folder 12)
  - Rules and Organization, 1997-1998 (Box 93, Folder 13)
  - Senate Rules of Procedure, 1997-1998 (Box 93, Folder 14)
  - Student Health Subcommittee, 1997-1998 (Box 93, Folder 15)
  - Bylaw 43, 1998-1999 (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Election of Officers, 1998-1999 (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Millenium Committee, 1998-1999 (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Organization & Governance (SCOG), 1998-1999 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Resolutions, 1998-1999 (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Rules and Organization, 1998-1999 (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Bylaw 31: University Senate, 1999-2000 (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - Bylaw 43: SSC, 1999-2000 (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - Election of Officers, 1999-2000 (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - Organization & Governance (SCOG), 1999-2000 (Box 94, Folder 10)
  - Resolutions, 1999-2000 (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - Rules & Organization, 1999-2000 (Box 94, Folder 12)
  - Senate Rules of Procedure, 1999-2000 (Box 94, Folder 13)
  - Bylaw 31: University Senate, 2000-2001 (Box 94, Folder 14)
  - Bylaw 43: SSC (2 versions SSC and UCSL), 2000-2001 (Box 94, Folder 15)
  - Organization and Governance, 2000-2001 (Box 94, Folder 16)
  - Resolutions, 2000-2001 (Box 94, Folder 17)
  - Rules and Organization, 2000-2001 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Bylaw 31: University Senate, 2001-2002 (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Bylaw 43: SSC (2 versions, SSC & UCSL), 2001-2002 (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - Bylaws, 2001, 2010-2015 (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - Election of Officers, 2001-2002 (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Organization and Governance (SCOG), 2001-2002 (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - Resolutions, 2001-2002 (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - Rules and Organization, 2001-2002 (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - Student Activities Board: Rules of Procedure, 2001-2002 (Box 96, Folder 9)
  - Bylaw 31: University Senate, 2002-2003 (Box 96, Folder 10)
  - Bylaw 43: SSC (Two Versions, SSC & UCSL), 2002-2003 (Box 96, Folder 11)
  - Non-Discrimination Policy: Proposal to Include Transgender Population, 2002-2003 (Box 96, Folder 12)
  - Organization and Governance, 2002-2003 (Box 96, Folder 13)
  - Protest and Dissent, Policy On, 2002-2003 (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Rules and Organization, 2002-2003 (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Senate Rules of Procedure, 2002-2003 (Box 94, Folder 18)
  - New York University Anti-Harassment Policy and Compliant Procedure, 2003 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Bylaw 31: University Senate, 2003-2004 (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Bylaw 43: SSC (Two Versions, SSC &UCSL), 2003-2004 (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Bylaws and Code of Ethics, 2003-2004 (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Election of Officers, 2003-2004 (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - Organization and Governance (SCOG), 2003-2004 (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - Protest and Dissent, Policy On, 2003-2004 (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - Resolutions, 2003-2004 (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - Rules and Organization, 2003-2004 (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - Bylaw 31: University Senate, 2004-2005 (Box 95, Folder 10)
  - Bylaw 43: SSC (2 ver. SSC & UCSL), 2004-2005 (Box 95, Folder 11)
  - Guest Speakers/Guest Policies, 2004-2005 (Box 95, Folder 12)
  - Organization and Governance (SCOG), 2004-2005 (Box 95, Folder 13)
  - Resolutions, 2004-2005 (Box 95, Folder 14)
  - Rules and Organization, 2004-2005 (Box 95, Folder 15)
  - Bylaw 31: University Senate, 2005-2006 (Box 95, Folder 16)
  - Bylaw 43: SSC (2 vers. SSC & UCSL), 2005-2006 (Box 95, Folder 17)
  - Organization and Governance (SCOG), 2005-2006 (Box 95, Folder 18)
  - Rules and Organization, 2005-2006 (Box 95, Folder 19)
  - University Charter & Bylaws, 2005-2006 (Box 95, Folder 20)
  - Organization and Governance (SCOG), 2006-2007 (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Resolutions, 2006-2007 (Box 97, Folder 4)